Inventory of the Citizens for Reagan Records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Citizens for Reagan (CFR) research functions, undated (Folder 37: 1)
  - Master catalogue, undated (Folder 37: 2)
    - Covert activities, undated (Folder 37: 24)
    - Crime, undated (Folder 37: 25)
    - Crime - Racial discrimination, undated (Folder 37: 26)
    - Cuba, 1975 (Folder 37: 27)
    - Cyprus, undated (Folder 37: 28)
    - Decentralization, 1976 (Folder 37: 29)
    - Democracy, undated (Folder 38: 1)
    - Détente, 1976 (Folder 38: 2)
    - Drug control, undated (Folder 38: 3)
    - Education, undated (Folder 38: 4)
    - Energy, undated (Folder 38: 5)
    - Energy development, undated (Folder 38: 6)
    - Environment, undated (Folder 38: 7)
    - Equal rights for women, 1976 (Folder 38: 8)
    - Federal debt, undated (Folder 38: 9)
    - Federal flood insurance, 1976 (Folder 38: 10)
    - Fishing limit - Two hundred mile, undated (Folder 38: 11)
    - Food stamps, undated (Folder 38: 12)
    - Food enterprise, undated (Folder 38: 13)
    - Gun control I and II, 1975-1976 (Folder 38: 14-15)
    - Helsinki, undated (Folder 38: 16)
    - Inflation, undated (Folder 38)
    - Food, undated (Folder 38: 17)
    - Paperwork, undated (Folder 38: 18)
    - Tax, undated (Folder 38: 19)
    - Insurance industry regulation, 1976 (Folder 38: 20)
    - Internal Revenue Service (IRS), undated (Folder 38: 21)
    - Italian elections, 1976 (Folder 38: 22)
    - Middle East, 1976 (Folder 38: 23)
    - Minority appointments, 1976 (Folder 38: 24-25)
    - National debt, 1976 (Folder 39: 1)
    - National health insurance, undated (Folder 39: 2)
    - No fault auto insurance, 1976 (Folder 39: 3)
    - Nuclear, undated (Folder 39: 4)
    - Oil, undated (Folder 39: 5)
    - Oil company divestiture, 1976 (Folder 39: 6)
    - Olympic games, 1976 (Folder 39: 7)
    - Panama/Cuba, 1976 (Folder 39: 8)
    - Panama Canal, undated (Folder 39: 9)
    - Peoples Republic of China, 1976 (Folder 39: 10)
    - Pollution, undated (Folder 39: 11)
    - Portugal, undated (Folder 39: 12)
    - Profits, undated (Folder 39: 13)
    - Public employee unionization, undated (Folder 39: 14)
    - Public employees, undated (Folder 39: 15)
    - Regulatory agencies, undated (Folder 39: 16)
    - Rhodesia I, 1976 (Folder 39: 17)
    - Rhodesia and South Africa, 1976 (Folder 39: 18)
    - Right to work, 1976 (Folder 39: 19)
    - Social Security 1 and 2, 1976 (Folder 39: 20-21)
    - Southeast Asia, undated (Folder 39: 22)
    - Spiritual commitment, 1976 (Folder 39: 23)
    - Strategic Arms Limitation Talk - Soviet Union, undated and 1976 (Folder 39: 24-25)
    - Tax limitation, undated (Folder 39: 26)
    - Tax bill, undated (Folder 39: 27)
    - Tax plan, undated (Folder 39: 28)
    - Transfer of federal programs, undated (Folder 39: 29)
    - Lyn Nofziger - United Republicans of California (UROC), 1975 (Folder 39: 30)
    - Ronald Reagan - United Republicans of California (UROC), 1975 (Folder 39: 31)
    - Unemployment, undated (Folder 39: 32)
    - USSR, undated (Folder 39: 33)
    - Veterans affairs, 1976 (Folder 39: 34)
    - Vietnam, 1976 (Folder 39: 35)
    - Welfare reform - Community work program, undated (Folder 39: 36)
    - Workers compensation, 1976 (Folder 39: 37)
  - Speeches and press releases, 1975-1976 (Folder 40)
    - 1975 October 21 - 1976 January 14 (Folder 40: 1)
    - 1976 January 15-April 22 (Folder 40: 2)
    - 1976 April 23-May 31 (Folder 40: 3)
    - 1976 June 1-August 15 (Folder 40: 4)
- Miscellaneous speeches, radio broadcasts, and news columns by Ronald Reagan, 1975-1976 (Folder 41)
  - "The Reagans and their Pastor," Christian Life, 1968 May (Folder 41: 1)
  - "How Ronald Reagan Governed California," by Charles D. Hobbs, National Review, 17 January 1975 (Folder 41: 2)
  - "Ronald Reagan's Real Record in California," U.S. News and World Report, 9 February 1976 (Folder 41: 3)
  - Ronald Reagan on "Meet the Press,", 7 March 1976 (Folder 41: 4)
  - "Where Reagan Stands," U.S. News and World Report, 31 May 1976 (Folder 41: 5)
  - Public opinion survey, 23 June 1976 (Folder 41: 6)
  - Drafts of speeches and articles, 1976 January 27-June 28 (Folder 41: 7)
  - Biographies of Ronald and Nancy Reagan, undated (Folder 41: 8)
  - "The Case for a Republican Legislature in California," undated, and reprints of radio programs - Viewpoints (Folder 41: 9)
  - Miscellany, 1975-1976 (Folder 41: 10-11)
- Youth for Reagan, 1973-1976 (Folder 42)
  - Budget, 1976 (Folder 42: 1)
  - Campaign (Folder 42)
    - General - Youth for Reagan, 1967-1976 (Folder 42: 2-3)
    - Florida, 1976 (Folder 42: 4)
    - Georgia, undated (Folder 42: 5)
    - Illinois, 1976 (Folder 42: 6)
    - Massachusetts, 1976 (Folder 42: 7)
    - Michigan, 1975-1976 (Folder 42: 8)
    - Minnesota, 1976 (Folder 42: 9)
    - Mississippi, 1975-1976 (Folder 42: 10)
    - Missouri, 1974-1976 (Folder 42: 11)
    - Montana, 1976 (Folder 42: 12)
    - Nebraska, 1975-1976 (Folder 42: 13)
    - Nevada, 1975-1976 (Folder 42: 14)
    - New Hampshire, 1976 (Folder 42: 15)
    - New Jersey, 1975-1976 and undated (Folder 42: 16)
    - New York, 1974-1976 (Folder 42: 17)
    - North Carolina, 1976 (Folder 42: 18)
    - Ohio, 1976 (Folder 42: 19)
    - Texas, undated (Folder 42: 20)
    - Virginia, 1975-1976 (Folder 42: 21)
    - Washington D.C., 1973 (Folder 43: 1)
    - Wisconsin, circa 1976 (Folder 43)
      - Alverno College, 1976 (Folder 43: 2)
      - Appleton West High School, undated (Folder 43: 3)
      - Brookfield East High School, undated (Folder 43: 4)
      - Cardinal Stritch College, 1976 (Folder 43: 5)
      - Cedarburg High School, undated (Folder 43: 6)
      - Concordia College, undated (Folder 43: 7)
      - Dominican High School, undated (Folder 43: 8)
      - Edgewood Catholic College, undated (Folder 43: 9)
      - La Follette High School, undated (Folder 43: 10)
      - Lakeland College, undated (Folder 43: 11)
      - Lawrence University, undated (Folder 43: 12)
      - Madison West High School, undated (Folder 43: 13)
      - Marquette High School, undated (Folder 43: 14)
      - Marquette University, undated (Folder 43: 15)
      - Memorial High School, undated (Folder 43: 16)
      - Messmer High School, undated (Folder 43: 17)
      - Milwaukee A. Technical College, undated (Folder 43: 18)
      - Muskego High School, undated (Folder 43: 19)
      - Nathan Hale High School, undated (Folder 43: 20)
      - Ripon College, undated (Folder 43: 21)
      - University of Wisconsin, undated (Folder 43)
      - Madison, undated (Folder 43: 22)
      - Milwaukee, undated (Folder 43: 23)
      - Oshkosh, undated (Folder 43: 24)
      - Waukesha County Technical Institute, undated (Folder 43: 25)
      - Wauwafosa East High School, undated (Folder 43: 26)
      - Whitefish Bay High School, undated (Folder 43: 27)
    - Fieldman availability form, undated (Folder 43: 28)
    - Recruitment manuals, undated (Folder 43: 29)
    - Resumes, 1975-1976 (Folder 43: 30)
    - Rosenfeldt, Stuart, undated (Folder 43: 31)
    - Stone, Roger, includes a photographic print of an unidentified individual, 1973-1976 (Folder 43: 32)
    - Young Americans for Freedom (YAF), 1975-1976 (Folder 43: 33)
    - Young Republican Leadership Conference, 1975 (Folder 43: 34)
- Primary, 1975-1976 (Folder 44)
  - General information, 1976 February-June (Folder 44: 1)
  - Total Republican primary votes, undated (Folder 44: 2)
  - By state, 1975-1976 (Folder 44)
    - Alabama, 1975 (Folder 44: 3)
    - Alaska, 1975 (Folder 44: 4)
    - Arkansas, undated (Folder 44: 5)
    - Arizona, 1976 (Folder 44: 6)
    - California, undated (Folder 44: 7)
    - Colorado, undated (Folder 44: 8)
    - Connecticut, 1975 (Folder 44: 9)
    - Delaware, 1975 (Folder 44: 10)
    - Georgia, 1975 (Folder 44: 11)
    - Hawaii, undated (Folder 44: 12)
    - Idaho, 1975 (Folder 44: 13)
    - Illinois, 1975-1976 (Folder 44: 14)
    - Indiana, undated (Folder 44: 15)
    - Iowa, 1975 (Folder 44: 16)
    - Kansas, 1975-1976 (Folder 44: 17)
    - Kentucky, 1975 (Folder 44: 18)
    - Louisiana, 1975 (Folder 44: 19)
    - Maine, undated (Folder 44: 20)
    - Maryland, 1975 (Folder 44: 21)
    - Massachusetts, 1975 (Folder 44: 22)
    - Michigan, 1975 (Folder 44: 23)
    - Minnesota, 1975 (Folder 44: 24)
    - Mississippi, undated (Folder 44: 25)
    - Missouri, undated (Folder 44: 26)
    - Montana, 1975 (Folder 44: 27)
    - Nebraska, 1975 (Folder 44: 28)
    - Nevada, undated (Folder 44: 29)
    - New Jersey, 1975 (Folder 44: 30)
    - New Mexico, 1975-1976 and undated (Folder 44: 31-32)
    - New Hampshire, 1975 and undated (Folder 44: 33)
    - New York, 1975-1976 (Folder 44: 34-35)
    - North Carolina, 1975-1976 (Folder 44: 36)
    - South Dakota, 1975-1976 (Folder 44: 37)
    - Ohio, 1975-1976 (Folder 44: 38)
    - Oklahoma, 1975-1976 (Folder 45: 1)
    - Oregon, 1975-1976 (Folder 45: 2)
    - Pennsylvania, 1975-1876 (Folder 45: 3)
    - Puerto Rico, 1975-1976 (Folder 45: 4)
    - Rhode Island, 1975-1976 (Folder 45: 5)
    - South Carolina, 1975-1976 (Folder 45: 6)
    - South Dakota, 1975-1976 (Folder 45: 7)
    - Tennessee, 1975-1976 (Folder 45: 8)
    - Texas, 1975-1976 (Folder 45: 9-10)
    - Utah, 1975-1976 (Folder 46: 1)
    - Vermont, 1975-1976 (Folder 46: 2)
    - Virgin Islands, 1976 (Folder 46: 3)
    - Washington, 1975-1976 (Folder 46: 4)
    - West Virginia, 1975-1976 (Folder 46: 5)
    - Wisconsin, 1975-1976 (Folder 46: 6)
    - Wyoming, 1975-1976 (Folder 46: 7)
- Senator Richard S. Schweiker, 1969-1976 (Folder 47)
  - "An Analysis of the New Politics: The Clark-Schweiker - A Campaign Study,", 1969 (Folder 47: 1)
  - Clippings, 1976 (Folder 47: 2)
  - Correspondence (Folder 47)
    - Letters to and from Richard S. Schweiker (Folder 47: 3)
    - Responses with incoming letters, 1976 (Folder 47: 4-6)
    - Responses with incoming letters, 1976 (Folder 48: 1-2)
    - Response, 1976 (Folder 48: 3)
  - "Governor Reagan's Gamble," Washington Post, 27 July 1976 (Folder 48: 4)
  - Nomination, 1976 (Folder 48: 5)
  - Political intelligence - Ratings, 1976 (Folder 48: 6)
  - Press releases, 1973-1976 (Folder 48: 7-8)
  - Press releases, 1973-1976 (Folder 49: 1-2)
  - Ronald Reagan's statement on selection, 1976 (Folder 49: 3)
  - Refunds, 1976 (Folder 49: 4)
  - Wire stories - Republican Convention, 1976 (Folder 49: 5)
- Republican National Convention, 1974-1976 (Folder 50)
  - "What's Wrong with America," An article by Ronald Reagan on U.S. economy, National Star, undated (Folder 50: 1)
  - Bell, Jeff, memoranda, 1974-1975 (Folder 50: 2)
  - Research correspondence, 1975-1976 (Folder 50: 3-4)
  - Buckley, Senator James L., 1976 (Folder 50: 5)
  - Cannon, Lou - Article, Washington Post, 1976 (Folder 50: 6)
  - Carter, James, Clippings, 1976 (Folder 50: 7)
  - Committee members, undated (Folder 50: 8)
  - Convention - General, 1976 (Folder 50: 9)
  - Convention, 17 August 1976 (Folder 50: 10)
  - Eidelberg, Paul, "Beyond Détente: Toward an American Foreign Policy," undated. Galley proof (Folder 50: 11)
  - Ford, President Gerald R., 1975-1976 (Folder 51)
    - Callaway, Bo memorandum regarding the President Ford Committee, 5 August 1975 (Folder 51: 1)
    - Ford electability, 1976 (Folder 51: 2)
    - Ford - Face the Nation, 1976 June 6. Transcript (Folder 51: 3)
    - General, 1975-1976 (Folder 51: 4-5)
    - Press, 1975-1976 (Folder 51: 6-7)
    - Gerald Ford solicitation letter, 16 February 1976 (Folder 51: 8)
    - Surrogate travel, circa 1976 (Folder 51: 9)
    - Use of incumbency, 1976 (Folder 51: 10)
    - Selection of Vice-President, undated (Folder 51: 11-12)
    - Wire Stories - Republican Convention, undated (Folder 51: 13)
  - Housing, 1975 (Folder 52: 1)
  - Investigation of the Ohio primary, 1976 (Folder 52: 2)
  - Testimony of Patrick M. Boarman to Foreign Relations Committee on amendment to International Monetary Fund articles, 1976 (Folder 52: 3)
  - Issues, 1976 (Folder 52)
    - Abortion, 1976 (Folder 52: 4)
    - "The China Issue, Anna Chennault, 1976 (Folder 52: 5)
    - Defense, 1976 (Folder 52: 6)
    - Health care, 1976 (Folder 52: 7)
    - Panama, undated (Folder 52: 8)
  - Letters, 1975-1976 (Folder 52)
    - Issues, answered, 1975-1976 (Folder 52: 9)
    - Ronald Reagan: "Why Am I Running," undated. Written after Texas primary (Folder 52: 10)
    - Ronald Reagan record, 1972-1976 (Folder 52: 11)
    - Requests filled, 1976 and undated (Folder 52: 12)
    - Rules committee - Connie Armitage, 1976 (Folder 52: 13)
    - Secretaries notebooks, undated (Folder 52: 14)
    - Selection of Richard, 1976 (Folder 52: 15)
    - Spiritual commitment letters, 1976 (Folder 52: 16)
    - To delegates from William A. Wilson, 1976 (Folder 52: 17)
    - To Mary Louise Smith regarding allocation of convention tickets, 1976 (Folder 52: 18)
    - To President Gerald Ford regarding California oil production difficulties, 1976 (Folder 52: 19)
    - Transmittal of materials from Citizens for Reagan to Molly Sturges (Folder 52: 20)
  - Memorandum to media - Jan McCoy, 1976 (Folder 52: 21)
  - Morgret, Peter M., "Informal Review of the 1952 Republican nominating Process and Its Lessons for Today,", undated (Folder 52: 22)
  - Phone bank, 1976 (Folder 52: 23)
  - Phone log - Ronald Reagan research office, Kansas city convention, 1976 (Folder 52: 24)
  - Press releases, 1976 (Folder 52: 25-27)
  - Ronald Reagan and Richard Schweiker convention news, 1976 (Folder 53: 1)
  - Ronald Reagan clippings, 1976 (Folder 53: 2)
  - Ronald Reagan's remarks to the convention, 1976 (Folder 53: 3)
  - Repackaging Richard Schweiker memorandum, 1976 (Folder 53: 4)
  - Resumes, 1975-1976 (Folder 53: 5)
  - Convention roll calls, 1976 (Folder 53: 6)
  - Rule 16C of the Republican National Convention, 1976 (Folder 53: 7)
  - Ronald Reagan committee appointments, 1976 (Folder 53: 8)
  - Schedules (Folder 53)
    - Ronald Reagan and Richard Schweiker, 1976 (Folder 53: 9)
    - Committees, 1976 (Folder 53: 10)
    - Ronald Reagan, 1976 May-June (Folder 53: 11)
  - Dr. Gloria Toote, Seconding speech, 1976 (Folder 53: 12)
  - Staff directory, 1976 (Folder 53: 13)
  - State briefing memorandum, undated (Folder 53: 14)
  - Support calls in Kansas City, undated (Folder 53: 15)
  - Vendors, 1974-1976 (Folder 53: 16)
  - "The Welfare Juggernaut," Patrick M. Boarman, Institute for Economic and Legal Analysis, undated (Folder 53: 17)
  - Wire stories, 1976 (Folder 54: 1-6)
  - Delegates, 1976 (Folder 54)
    - By state, 1976 (Folder 54)
      - General, 1976 (Folder 54: 7-9)
      - Alabama - Arkansas (Folder 54: 10)
      - California (Folder 54: 11)
      - Colorado - Illinois (Folder 55: 1)
      - Indiana - Louisiana (Folder 55: 2)
      - Maine - Nebraska (Folder 55: 3)
      - Nevada - North Dakota (Folder 55: 4)
      - Ohio - Texas (Folder 55: 5)
      - Utah - Virgin Islands (Folder 55: 6)
    - Counts, 1976 (Folder 56: 1)
    - Letters - Dave Keene, 1976 (Folder 56: 2)
      - By state, 1976 (Folder 56)
        - Illinois (Folder 56: 3)
        - Louisiana (Folder 56: 4)
        - Mississippi (Folder 56: 5)
        - New Jersey (Folder 56: 6)
        - New York (Folder 56: 7)
        - Pennsylvania (Folder 56: 8)
        - Tennessee (Folder 56: 9)
        - Virginia (Folder 56: 10)
    - Delegate list, undated (Folder 56: 11)
    - Material book - President Gerald Ford committee, 14 July 1976 (Folder 56: 12)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Folder 56: 13)
    - Regional responsibilities, undated (Folder 56: 14)
    - Uncommitted, 1976 (Folder 56: 15)
    - Wire stories, 1976 (Folder 56: 16)
  - Delegations, 1976 and undated (Folder 56)
    - Chairman - Convention hotel locations, undated (Folder 56: 17)
    - Iowa, 1976 (Folder 56: 18)
    - Kansas, 1976 (Folder 56: 19)
    - Nebraska, 1976 (Folder 56: 20)
    - New Jersey, undated (Folder 56: 21)
    - North Dakota, 1976 (Folder 56: 22)
    - South Carolina, 1976 (Folder 56: 23)
    - Tennessee, 1976 (Folder 56: 24)
    - Wisconsin, 1976 (Folder 56: 25)
  - Alternate mailing list labels, undated (Folder 57)
  - Platform (Folder 58)
    - Analysis package, 1976 (Folder 58: 1)
    - Committee - Ronald Reagan's letter to members of the platform committee, 14 August 1976 (Folder 58: 2)
    - Domestic, undated. Draft (Folder 58: 3)
    - Statement by Jesse Helms, 11 August 1976 (Folder 58: 4)
    - Material, 1976 (Folder 58: 5)
    - Planks, undated (Folder 58: 6)
    - Platform planks as proposed and adopted, 1976 (Folder 58: 7)
    - Presentations, 1976 (Folder 58: 8-9)
    - Speeches, 1976 (Folder 58: 10)
    - Subcommittee (Folder 58)
    - Membership, undated (Folder 58: 11)
    - Materials, 1976 (Folder 58: 12-13)
    - Testimony of the Council of 100 - An Organization of Black Republicans, 10 August 1976 (Folder 58: 14)
    - Wire stories, undated (Folder 58: 15)
- Correspondence (Folder 59)
  - John P. Sears - Dave Keene, 1976 June (Folder 59)
    - Alabama (Folder 59: 1)
    - Alaska (Folder 59: 2)
    - Arizona (Folder 59: 3)
    - Arkansas (Folder 59: 4)
    - California (Folder 59: 5)
    - Colorado (Folder 59: 6)
    - Connecticut (Folder 59: 7)
    - Florida (Folder 59: 8)
    - Georgia (Folder 59: 9)
    - Hawaii (Folder 59: 10)
    - Idaho (Folder 59: 11)
    - Illinois (Folder 59: 12)
    - Indiana (Folder 59: 13)
    - Iowa (Folder 59: 14)
    - Kansas (Folder 59: 15)
    - Kentucky (Folder 59: 16)
    - Louisiana (Folder 59: 17)
    - Maine (Folder 59: 18)
    - Maryland (Folder 59: 19)
    - Massachusetts (Folder 59: 20)
    - Michigan (Folder 59: 21)
    - Minnesota (Folder 59: 22)
    - Mississippi (Folder 59: 23)
    - Missouri (Folder 59: 24)
    - Montana (Folder 59: 25)
    - Nebraska (Folder 59: 26)
    - Nevada (Folder 59: 27)
    - New Hampshire (Folder 59: 28)
    - New Jersey (Folder 59: 29)
    - New Mexico (Folder 59: 30)
    - New York (Folder 59: 31)
    - North Carolina (Folder 59: 32)
    - North Dakota (Folder 59: 33)
    - Ohio (Folder 59: 34)
    - Oklahoma (Folder 59: 35)
    - Oregon (Folder 59: 36)
    - Pennsylvania (Folder 59: 37)
    - Rhode Island (Folder 59: 38)
    - South Carolina (Folder 59: 39)
    - South Dakota (Folder 59: 40)
    - Tennessee (Folder 59: 41)
    - Texas (Folder 59: 42)
    - Utah (Folder 59: 43)
    - Virginia (Folder 59: 44)
    - Washington (Folder 59: 45)
    - Washington, D.C. (Folder 59: 46)
    - West Virginia (Folder 59: 47)
    - Wisconsin (Folder 59: 48)
    - Wyoming (Folder 59: 49)
  - Paul Laxalt (Folder 60)
    - General, Includes 2 photographic prints depicting Jim Adcox, 1975 July-December (Folder 60: 1)
    - January-February, 1976 (Folder 60: 2)
    - January-July, 1976 (Folder 60: 3)
    - March, 1976 (Folder 60: 4-6)
    - April, 1976 (Folder 60: 7-8)
    - May, 1976 (Folder 60: 9-11)
    - June, 1976 (Folder 60: 12)
  - Support/donation letters, 1976 March 17-May 15 (Folder 60: 13)
  - Letters from abroad, 1976 May 5-August 3 (Folder 60: 14)
  - Responses of John P. Sears to contribution letters - Primarily after March 31 speech, 1976 March 15-April 30 (Folder 60: 15)
  - Responses of John P. Sears (Folder 61)
    - Alabama, 1975-1976 (Folder 61: 1)
    - Alaska, 1975-1976 (Folder 61: 2)
    - Arizona, 1975-1976 (Folder 61: 3)
    - Arkansas, 1975-1976 (Folder 61: 4)
    - California (Folder 61)
      - June-August, 1975 (Folder 61: 5)
      - September, 1975 (Folder 61: 6)
      - October, 1975 (Folder 61: 7)
      - November, 1975 (Folder 61: 8)
      - December, 1975 (Folder 61: 9)
      - January, 1976 (Folder 62: 1)
      - February-June, 1976 (Folder 62: 2)
    - Canada, 1976 (Folder 62: 3)
    - Colorado, 1975-1976 (Folder 62: 4)
    - Connecticut, 1975-1976 (Folder 62: 5-6)
    - Delaware, 1975-1976 (Folder 62: 7-8)
    - District of Columbia, 1975-1976 (Folder 62: 9-11)
    - Florida, 1975-1976 (Folder 62: 12-13)
    - Florida, 1975-1976 (Folder 63: 1-3)
    - Hawaii, 1975-1976 (Folder 63: 4)
    - Idaho, 1976 (Folder 63: 5)
    - Illinois, 1975-1976 (Folder 63: 6-7)
    - Indiana, 1975-1976 (Folder 63: 8)
    - Maine, 1975-1976 (Folder 63: 9)
    - Maryland, 1976 (Folder 63: 10)
    - Massachusetts, 1975-1976 (Folder 63: 11)
    - Michigan, 1975-1976 (Folder 63: 12)
    - Mississippi, 1975 (Folder 64: 1)
    - Missouri, 1976 (Folder 64: 2)
    - Montana, 1976 (Folder 64: 3)
    - Nevada, 1976 (Folder 64: 4)
    - New Hampshire, 1975-1976 (Folder 64: 5)
    - New Jersey, 1975-1976 (Folder 64: 6)
    - New Mexico, 1976 (Folder 64: 7)
    - New York, 1975-1976 (Folder 64: 8-9)
    - New York, 1975 (Folder 65: 1)
    - North Carolina, 1975-1976 (Folder 65: 2)
    - Ohio, 1975-1976 (Folder 65: 3-8)
    - Oregon, 1976 (Folder 65: 9)
    - Pennsylvania, 1975-1976 (Folder 66: 1-4)
    - Puerto Rico, 1975 (Folder 66: 5)
    - Tennessee, 1975-1976 (Folder 66: 6-7)
    - Texas, 1975-1976 (Folder 67: 1)
    - Utah, 1976 (Folder 67: 2)
    - Vermont, 1975-1976 (Folder 67: 3)
    - Washington, 1975-1976 (Folder 67: 4)
    - Wisconsin, 1975 (Folder 67: 5)
    - West Virginia, 1975-1976 (Folder 67: 6)
    - Wyoming, 1976 (Folder 67: 7)
    - King Leka of Albania, 1975 (Folder 67: 8)
    - Miscellany, 1975-1976 (Folder 67: 9)
  - John P. Sears chronological correspondence (Folder 68)
    - July. Includes letters by Ronald Reagan, 1975 (Folder 68: 1)
    - August, 1975 (Folder 68: 2)
    - September, 1975 (Folder 68: 3)
    - October, 1975 (Folder 68: 4)
    - November, 1975 (Folder 68: 5)
    - December, 1975 (Folder 68: 6)
    - March, 1976 (Folder 68: 7)
    - April, 1976 (Folder 68: 8)
    - May, 1976 (Folder 68: 9-12)
    - June, 1976 (Folder 69: 1-7)
    - July, 1976 (Folder 70: 1-5)
    - August, 1976 (Folder 70: 6)
    - February-March. Includes letters dated January, 1976 (Folder 71: 1)
    - April, 1976 (Folder 71: 2-3)
    - May, 1976 (Folder 71: 4-8)
    - May, 1976 (Folder 72: 1)
    - May-June, 1976 (Folder 72: 2)
    - May-July. Includes 2 sound discs, undated 1976 (Folder 72: 3)
    - June, 1976 (Folder 72: 4-6)
    - June, 1976 (Folder 73: 1)
    - July, 1976 (Folder 73: 2-3)
  - Correspondence between Frank A. Hoff and others, 1936-1979 (Folder 73: 4)
  - John P. Sears correspondence (Folder 74)
    - December, 1975 (Folder 74: 1)
    - January, 1976 (Folder 74: 2)
    - February, 1976 (Folder 74: 3)
    - March, 1976 (Folder 74: 4-6)
    - April, 1976 (Folder 74: 7-8)
    - July, 1976 (Folder 74: 9)
    - July, 1976 (Folder 75: 1)
    - July-August (emphasis on Schweiker nomination), 1976 (Folder 75: 2-3)
    - August, 1976 (Folder 75: 4)
    - May, 1976 (Folder 76: 1-4)
    - June, 1976 (Folder 76: 5-6)
    - June, 1976 (Folder 77: 1-3)
    - July, 1976 (Folder 77: 4-8)
    - August, 1976 (Folder 77: 9)
    - Alabama, 1976 (Folder 78: 1)
    - Alaska, 1976 (Folder 78: 2)
    - Arizona, 1976 (Folder 78: 3)
    - Arkansas, 1976 (Folder 78: 4)
    - California, 1976 (Folder 78: 5-6)
    - Colorado, 1976 (Folder 78: 7)
    - Connecticut, 1976 (Folder 78: 8)
    - Delaware, 1976 (Folder 78: 9)
    - Florida, 1976 (Folder 78: 10)
    - Georgia, 1976 (Folder 78: 11)
    - Hawaii, 1976 (Folder 78: 12)
    - Idaho, 1976 (Folder 78: 13)
    - Illinois, 1976 (Folder 78: 14)
    - Indiana, 1976 (Folder 78: 15)
    - Iowa, 1976 (Folder 79: 1)
    - Kansas, 1976 (Folder 79: 2)
    - Kentucky, 1976 (Folder 79: 3)
    - Louisiana, 1976 (Folder 79: 4)
    - Maine, 1976 (Folder 79: 5)
    - Maryland, 1976 (Folder 79: 6)
    - Massachusetts, 1976 (Folder 79: 7)
    - Michigan, 1976 (Folder 79: 8)
    - Minnesota, 1976 (Folder 79: 9)
    - Mississippi, 1976 (Folder 79: 10)
    - Missouri, 1976 (Folder 79: 11)
    - Montana, 1976 (Folder 79: 12)
    - Nebraska, 1976 (Folder 79: 13)
    - Nevada, 1976 (Folder 79: 14)
    - New Hampshire, 1976 (Folder 79: 15)
    - New Jersey, 1976 (Folder 79: 16)
    - New Mexico, 1976 (Folder 79: 17)
    - New York, 1976 (Folder 79: 18)
    - North Carolina, 1976 (Folder 79: 19)
    - North Dakota, 1976 (Folder 79: 20)